in this problem
we need to write a method a sign name
that will result in both of the test
cases we've been given
outputting true in our test cases on
lines 1 and
2 we compare the return value of the
assign name method
to the strings kevin and bob
and output the result of that comparison
so when we run our code we want to see
an output of true for both test cases
and first let's begin by just working
with our first test case
our method should be called assign name
and on line three you can see that we
pass the string kevin to our method as
an
argument so we'll give our method
a parameter called name
and the problem description tells us
that the methods return value should be
the value of the argument
so we'll simply return name from our
method
let's run our code with our first test
case and see whether or not the output
is true
and it is
so we're seeing the expected behavior
here
for our first test case on line five
now let's run our code with our second
test case as well
and see if we output true again
you can see that although we still
output true when we run our first test
case
our second test case raises an exception
an argument error we passed zero
arguments
to the method assign name however the
method was expecting us to pass one
argument
so let's go back and look at our code
you can see on line six we didn't pass
any arguments to assign
name however we are expecting a return
value of bob
from our method now the problem
description tells us that
our method should accept one argument
as it does in our first test case on
line 5
but doesn't require it the parameter
should default to the string
bob if no argument is given
so what we need to do here is define a
default parameter for
our method our problem description tells
us that
in this case the default parameter
should be the string bob
so on line one we will define a default
parameter for our method
next to the parameter name we'll place
an equal sign
and then the value of the default
parameter
now if we fail to pass in an argument
our method will return
bob otherwise our method will use the
argument that we passed in such as
kevin on line five
so let's run our code again and see if
we're outputting true for both test
cases
and we are
so it's possible to define a default
parameter for your method
if you need that flexibility
you